A Guide to the National Association of Alcoholism and Drug Abuse Counselors, 1970-2000
Library of Virginia
- Publications (Box 112-116)
  - 1st and 2nd Special Reports to Congress on Alcohol and Health (Box 112, Folder 8)
  - - Guide Lines for Admission of Alcoholics to Hospitals (Box 112, Folder 9)
  - - Alcoholism: Clinical and Experimental Research (Box 112, Folder 9)
  - - Addictions Publications (Box 112, Folder 9)
  - - A Growing Concern (Box 112, Folder 9)
  - - Johnson Institute Resources (Box 112, Folder 9)
  - - Standards for Halfway House Alcoholism Programs (Box 112, Folder 10)
  - - Residential Drug-free Manual (Box 112, Folder 10)
  - - Alcohol & Alcoholism: Problems, Programs, & Progress (Box 112, Folder 10)
  - - In Focus: Alcohol and Alcoholism Audiovisual Guide (Box 112, Folder 10)
  - Directory of Addiction Professionals--1986-87, 1988-89 (Box 112, Folder 11)
  - - National Clearinghouse for Alcohol Information (Box 112, Folder 12)
  - - The Role of the Rehabilitation Counselor (Box 112, Folder 12)
  - - Judge's Guide for Alcohol Offenders (Box 112, Folder 12)
  - - Prevention Resources (vol. 5, no. 3--Fall 1981) (Box 112, Folder 12)
  - - The Unseen Crisis: Blacks and Alcohol (Box 112, Folder 12)
  - - The Nurse and the Alcoholic (Box 112, Folder 12)
  - - Rehabilitation of the Drug Abuser (Box 112, Folder 13)
  - - Title XX Handbook for Alcohol, Drug Abuse, and Mental Health Treatment Programs (Box 112, Folder 13)
  - The Whole College Catalog About Drinking (Box 112, Folder 14)
  - Proceedings of the First Annual Alcoholism Conference of the National Institute on Alcohol Abuse and Alcoholism (Box 112, Folder 15)
  - The Quarterly vol. 1, no. 1; vol. 2, nos. 1-3 (Sept. 1977-Oct. 1978) (Box 113, Folder 1)
  - - The Counselor vol. 1, no. 1 (June 1979)-vol. 4 (Box 113, Folder 2-3)
  - - The Counselor vol. 1, no. 8 (Oct. 1982) (missing vol. 4, no. 7) (Box 113, Folder 2-3)
  - The Counselor March/April 1983 (vol. 1, no. 2) -Nov/Dec 1991 (missing vol. 1, no. 1 and vol. 2, no. 5) (Box 113, Folder 4-17)
  - The Counselor Jan/Feb 1992-Nov/Dec 1996 (Box 114, Folder 1-10)
  - - ACA Journal (Spring 1988) (Box 114, Folder 11)
  - - Alcohol Drugs, & Driving (vol. 2, nos. 3-4, July-Dec 1986; vol. 7, no. 1, January-March 1991) (Box 114, Folder 11)
  - - Alcohol Quarterly (vol. 1--Spring 1988) (Box 114, Folder 11)
  - - Alcoholism & Addiction (Dec. 1987) (Box 114, Folder 11)
  - - Alcoholism Treatment Quarterly (vol. 1, no. 3--Fall 1984) (Box 114, Folder 12)
  - - AMERSA Substance Abuse (vol. 6, no. 1; vol. 9, no. 1, vol. 10, no. 4) (Box 114, Folder 12)
  - - Almacan (vol. 15, no. 1; vol. 16, no. 2) (Box 114, Folder 12)
  - - Bottom Line (vol. 9, no. 3) (Box 114, Folder 13)
  - - Digest of Alcoholism Theory & Application (vol. 1, no. 1; vol. 2, no. 1 (Box 114, Folder 13)
  - - Drug and Alcohol Dependence (vol. 1, no. 3) (Box 114, Folder 13)
  - - EAP Digest (May/June 1983; July/Aug 1984) (Box 114, Folder 14)
  - - EAPA Exchange (vol. 19, no. 10) (Box 114, Folder 14)
  - - EEAETP Information Bulletin (vol. 2, no. 5) (Box 114, Folder 14)
  - - Employee Assistance Quarterly (vol. 1, no. 2) (Box 114, Folder 14)
  - - Focus (Nov/Dec 1987) (Box 114, Folder 14)
  - - Journal of Alcohol and Drug Education (vol. 25, no. 2) (Box 114, Folder 15)
  - - Journal of Studies on Alcohol (vol. 36, no. 5, vol. 45, no. 4) (Box 114, Folder 15)
  - - Labor-Management Alcoholism Journal (vol. 4, no. 3) (Box 114, Folder 16)
  - - MADD in Action (vol. 8, no. 3) (Box 114, Folder 16)
  - - Ms. (Feb. 1987) (Box 114, Folder 16)
  - - Professional Counselor (vol. 3, no. 1) (Box 114, Folder 16)
  - - Recovery Life (March-April) (Box 114, Folder 16)
  - - Report Series (vol. 35, no. F; vol. 43, no. 1) (Box 114, Folder 16)
  - - U. S. Journal (vol. 1, no. 12; vol. 3, no. 5) (Box 114, Folder 16)
  - NAADAC Newsletter (vol. 1, no. 1) (Box 114, Folder 17)
  - The Alcoholism Report (vol. 1, issue 1-issue 24-missing issue 8) (Box 115, Folder 1)
  - The Alcoholism Report (vol. 2, issue 1-issue 24) (Box 115, Folder 2)
  - The Alcoholism Report (vol. 3, issue 1-issue 24-missing issue 14) (Box 115, Folder 3)
  - The Alcoholism Report (vol. 4, issue 1-issue 24-missing issue 5) (Box 115, Folder 4)
  - The Alcoholism Report (vol. 5, issue 1-issue 24) (Box 115, Folder 5)
  - The Alcoholism Report (vol. 6, issue 1-issue 24) (Box 115, Folder 6)
  - The Alcoholism Report (vol. 7, issue 1-issue 24) (Box 115, Folder 7)
  - The Alcoholism Report (vol. 8, issue 1-issue 24) (Box 115, Folder 8)
  - The Alcoholism Report (vol. 9, issue 1-issue 24) (Box 116, Folder 1)
  - The Alcoholism Report (vol. 10, issue 1-issue 24-missing issue 21) (Box 116, Folder 2)
  - The Alcoholism Report (vol. 11, issue 1-issue 24) (Box 116, Folder 3)
  - The Alcoholism Report (vol. 12, issue 1-issue 24) (Box 116, Folder 4)
  - The Alcoholism Report (vol. 13, issue 1-issue 24) (Box 116, Folder 5)
  - The Alcoholism Report (vol. 14, issue 1-issue 24-missing issue 23) (Box 116, Folder 6)
  - The Alcoholism Report (vol. 15, issue 1-issue 24-missing issues 4, 5, 9, 11, 12, 13, 14, 16, 17) (Box 116, Folder 7)
  - The Alcoholism Report (vol. 16, issue 1-issue 24-missing issues 2, 15, 18, 19) (Box 116, Folder 8)
  - The Alcoholism Report (vol. 17, issue 1-issue 12-missing issues [5], 6, 7, 9, 10, 11-2nd issue 3 and issue 4 misnumbered) (Box 116, Folder 9)
  - The Alcoholism Report (vol. 18, issue 2-issue 9-missing issue 1) (Box 116, Folder 10)